<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shin Package Manager - Docs</title>
    <link>https://newdawn0.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shin Package Manager - Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://newdawn0.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Common Errors</title>
      <link>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Overview: This post will guide you through all the possible available errors that can occur when using Shin. First this quick guide will cover the install errors. Next come the uninstall errors. And what to do if you find a new undocumented error. Another easy way to decect erros is the arrow is usually depicted in a cyan/blue color. Although not all cyan/blue arrows are errors.
Install Errors:  Install Errors Uninstall Errors Unavailable Package Errors What to do with undocumented errors  Install Errors: There two types of install errors that can occur in the installation process Because Shin always checks if a package is already installed to avoid duplication or overwriting of pakcages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing packages</title>
      <link>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Overview: This post will guide you through installing packages with 2 different methods and installing multiple packages. The first part of the post will go through the general installation process of packages without choosing a package manager specifically. The second part of the post will guide you through installing packages with a specific package manager. And finally the last part will show you how to install multiple packages with and without a package manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listing packages and package managers</title>
      <link>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Overview: This post will guide you show you how to list all installed Packages and Package managers
Table of Contents:  Listing all installed packages Listing all installed package managers Listing all installed packages with their package managers  Listing all installed packages: To list all installed packages you can use one of the following commands:
sudo shin list sudo shin list-packages sudo shin -l Output: Listing all installed package managers: To list all installed package managers you can use one of the following commands: Be aware that this list of package managers unlike the the package list does not change it is written on install of shin and will not change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for packages</title>
      <link>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Overview: This post will guide you show you how to list all installed Packages and Package managers
Table of Contents:  Listing all installed packages Listing all installed package managers  Listing all installed packages: There are often multiple ways to archieve something with shin. Most commonly there you have the option to type the full word or just the first letter(s) but starting with a minus. Anyway here are the two ways to uninstall a package with Shin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstalling packages</title>
      <link>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://newdawn0.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>Overview: This post will guide you through uninstalling packages one by one and uninstalling multiple packages
Table of Contents:  Uninstalling packages one by one Uninstalling multiple packages  Uninstalling packages one by one: There are often multiple ways to archieve something with shin. Most commonly there you have the option to type the full word or just the first letter(s) but starting with a minus. Anyway here are the two ways to uninstall a package with Shin</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
